Guide to the Baldwin Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
African Americans; Archaeology; Business; Education -- United States; Education; Families; Law; Mothers and daughters; Public welfare; Social sciences; Women -- United States; Women; Boston (Mass.) -- Social life and customs; Chicago (Ill.) -- History; Connecticut -- Religious life and customs; Connecticut; Europe; Germany; Middle West; New Haven (Conn.); New Haven (Conn.) -- Politics and government; New Haven (Conn.) -- Social life and customs; New York (N.Y.); New York (N.Y.) -- Politics and government; New York (State); United States -- Foreign relations; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; United States -- History -- Colonial period, ca. 1600-1775; United States -- History -- Revolution, 1775-1783; United States -- Politics and government; Washington (D.C.) -- Social life and customs; West (U.S.); Account books; Deeds; Diaries; Photographs; Sermons; Clergy; Lawyers; Baldwin, Ebenezer, 1745-1776; Baldwin, Ebenezer, 1790-1837; Baldwin, Edward Law, 1822-1848; Baldwin, Elizabeth Sherman Burr, 1765-1850; Baldwin, Emily Pitkin Perkins, 1796-1874; Baldwin, George William, 1832-1930; Baldwin, Henry De Forest, 1862-1947; Baldwin, Rebecca Sherman, 1764-1795; Baldwin, Rebecca, 1688-1713; Baldwin, Roger S. (Roger Sherman), 1793-1863; Baldwin, Roger Sherman, 1826-1856; Baldwin, Roger Sherman, 1869-1956; Baldwin, Simeon E. (Simeon Eben), 1840-1927; Baldwin, Simeon, 1761-1851; Baldwin, Susan Winchester; Day, Thomas, 1777-1855; Foster, Dwight, 1828-1884; Foster, Emily Perkins Baldwin; Foster, Henrietta Perkins Baldwin, 1830-1910; Gifford, Ellen Marett; Hillhouse, William, 1757-1833; Marett, Philip, 1792-1869; Marsh, Jonathan, 1685-1747; Perkins, Enoch, 1760-1828; Sherman, Martha; Staples, Seth Perkins, 1776-1861; Whitney, Elizabeth Wooster Baldwin, 1824-1912; Winchester, Charlotte; Baldwin family; Burr family; Mears family; Perkins family; Sherman family; Winchester family; Fairfield State Hospital (Newtown, Conn.); Derby Fishing Company; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1781; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1861; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Clio Society
- General Correspondence, 1595-1947; Series I; 26 linear feet (62 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence and related papers arranged chronologically, with undated items filed at the end of the series.
  - 1595-1772 (Box 1, Folder 1-15)
  - 1773-1782 (Box 2, Folder 16-32)
  - 1783-1786 (Box 3, Folder 33-50)
  - 1787-1791 (Box 4, Folder 51-72)
  - 1792-1795 July (Box 5, Folder 73-88)
  - 1795 August-1799 (Box 6, Folder 89-97)
  - 1800-1802 (Box 7, Folder 98-106)
  - 1803-1805 May (Box 8, Folder 107-117)
  - 1805 June-1810 (Box 9, Folder 118-128)
  - 1811-1813 (Box 10, Folder 129-139)
  - 1814-1816 May (Box 11, Folder 140-149)
  - 1816 June-1818 (Box 12, Folder 150-159)
  - 1819-1821 May (Box 13, Folder 160-168)
  - 1821 June-1823 (Box 14, Folder 169-177)
  - 1824-1825 (Box 15, Folder 178-185)
  - 1826-1827 (Box 16, Folder 186-192)
  - 1828-1829 (Box 17, Folder 193-200)
  - 1830-1832 (Box 18, Folder 201-212)
  - 1833-1836 April (Box 19, Folder 213-223)
  - 1836 May-1838 February (Box 20, Folder 224-234)
  - 1838 March-1840 (Box 21, Folder 235-248)
    Includes a deposition of James Covey concerning the Amistad captives held in the New Haven County Jail, 1839 October 4.
  - 1841-1842 September (Box 22, Folder 249-260)
    - Cinque (also known as Joseph Cinqué and Sengbe Pieh) letter, original, 1841 February 9 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - 1842 October-1844 (Box 23, Folder 261-275)
  - 1845 (Box 24, Folder 276-285)
  - 1846-1847 August (Box 25, Folder 286-299)
  - 1847 September-1848 May (Box 26, Folder 300-309)
  - 1848 June-1849 February (Box 27, Folder 310-321)
  - 1849 March-1850 March (Box 28, Folder 322-333)
  - 1850 April-December (Box 29, Folder 334-345)
  - 1851-1852 April (Box 30, Folder 346-357)
  - 1852 May-1853 (Box 31, Folder 358-371)
  - 1854-1856 October (Box 32, Folder 372-386)
  - 1856 November-1859 (Box 33, Folder 387-400)
  - 1860-1862 April (Box 34, Folder 401-413)
  - 1862 May-1864 July (Box 35, Folder 414-428)
  - 1864 August-1866 (Box 36, Folder 429-442)
  - 1867-1868 (Box 37, Folder 443-456)
  - 1869-1871 April (Box 38, Folder 457-468)
  - 1871 May-1872 April (Box 39, Folder 469-480)
  - 1872 May-1873 August (Box 40, Folder 481-491)
  - 1873 September-1875 June (Box 41, Folder 492-503)
  - 1875 July-1876 (Box 42, Folder 504-513)
  - 1877-1879 (Box 43, Folder 514-531)
  - 1880-1882 June (Box 44, Folder 532-544)
  - 1882 July-1884 (Box 45, Folder 545-559)
  - 1885-1886 (Box 46, Folder 560-574)
  - 1887-1888 October (Box 47, Folder 575-590)
  - 1888 November-1890 (Box 48, Folder 591-606)
  - 1891-1892 April (Box 49, Folder 607-619)
  - 1892 May-1893 May (Box 50, Folder 620-631)
  - 1893 June-1894 July (Box 51, Folder 632-647)
  - 1894 August-1896 (Box 52, Folder 648-664)
  - 1897-1898 August (Box 53, Folder 665-681)
  - 1898 September-1900 (Box 54, Folder 682-695)
  - 1901-1904 (Box 55, Folder 696-712)
  - 1905-1908 (Box 56, Folder 713-727)
  - 1909-1910 November (Box 57, Folder 728-741)
  - 1910 November-1913 (Box 58, Folder 742-756)
  - 1914-1916 (Box 59, Folder 757-770)
  - 1917-1924 (Box 60, Folder 771-783)
  - 1925-1947 (Box 61, Folder 784-798)
  - Undated (Box 62, Folder 799-807)
- Ebenezer Baldwin (1745-1776), 1760-1776; Series II; 1 linear foot (3 boxes)
  This series contains material arranged alphabetically by record type.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 63, Folder 808)
  - Diary, 1763-1764 (Box 63, Folder 809)
  - Diploma, 1763 (Box 63, Folder 810)
  - Financial papers, 1770s (Box 63, Folder 811)
  - Notebooks
    - Eclipse, 1761 (Box 63, Folder 812)
    - Greek grammar, 1760 (Box 63, Folder 813)
    - Mathematics, 1761 (Box 63, Folder 814)
  - Notes, undated (Box 63, Folder 815-816)
  - Obituary: Jonathan Lyman, 1766 (Box 63, Folder 817)
  - Papers, undated (Box 63, Folder 818)
  - Religious Writings, undated (Box 63, Folder 819)
  - Sermons: 1-41, 1766-1776 (Box 64)
  - Sermons: 142-189; miscellanea, 1766-1776 (Box 65)
  - Susquehanna Company account, 1775 (Box 212, Folder 6)
- Ebenezer Baldwin (1790-1837), 1807-1829; Series III; 0.25; (1 box)
  - Financial and legal documents and Yale College diploma, 1811-1829 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Notebook: Yale University, 1807-1808 (Box 66, Folder 820)
  - Orations, 1808, undated (Box 66, Folder 821)
  - Writings and letters, undated (Box 66, Folder 822-823)
- Simeon Baldwin (1761-1851), 1779-1879; Series IV; 3 linear feet (7 boxes)
  - Account books, 1786-1808 (Box 67, Folder 824-827)
  - Account books, 1803-1831 (Box 68, Folder 828-830)
  - Addresses, 1792 (Box 69, Folder 831)
  - Anti-slavery petition, undated (Box 69, Folder 832)
  - Bank books, 1796-1836 (Box 69, Folder 833)
  - Cash books, 1788-1851 (Box 69, Folder 834-837)
  - Checks, 1818-1849 (Box 69, Folder 838-840)
  - Church announcements, 1815; 1835 (Box 70, Folder 841)
  - Court dockets, 1786-1834 (Box 70, Folder 842-844)
  - Diploma, 1781 (Box 70, Folder 845)
  - Estate records, 1851-1879 (Box 70, Folder 846-847)
  - Journals, 1782-1791 (Box 70, Folder 848-849)
  - Legal and financial documents, 1779-1851 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Legal cases, undated (Box 71, Folder 850)
  - Legal notebook, 1785 (Box 71, Folder 851)
  - Letterbook, undated (Box 71, Folder 852)
  - Notes and receipts, 1798-1857 (Box 72, Folder 853-863)
  - Play, undated (Box 73, Folder 864)
  - Printed material, 1822 (Box 73, Folder 865)
  - Student essays, undated (Box 73, Folder 866)
  - Student lecture notes, undated (Box 73, Folder 867)
  - Writings, undated (Box 73, Folder 868-870)
  - Miscellanea, undated (Box 73, Folder 871-872)
  - Oversize material, 1835-1841 (Box 211A)
    Comprises maps of land lots in the city of New Haven belonging to Simeon Baldwin, house plans (possibly sketches by Simeon Baldwin, or by the architect L.W. Robinson for the Eli Whitney house on Elm Street), and sketch of houses adjacent to the home of Simeon Baldwin.
- Roger Sherman Baldwin (1826-1856), 1830-1859; Series V; 0.5; (1 box)
  - Autograph book, 1847 (Box 74, Folder 873)
  - Diary, 1842 September-November (Box 74, Folder 874)
  - Financial papers, 1840s (Box 74, Folder 875)
  - Legal and financial documents and Yale diploma, Circa 1830-1859 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 74, Folder 876)
  - Student notebooks, undated (Box 74, Folder 877)
  - Writings, undated (Box 74, Folder 878)
- Simeon Eben Baldwin (1840-1927), 1617-1977; Series VI; 23.25 linear feet (51 boxes)
  - Account books
    - Personal, 1901-1923 (Box 75, Folder 879)
    - Morning News, 1889-1896 (Box 75, Folder 880)
  - Anecdotes, undated (Box 75, Folder 881-882)
  - Appointment books, 1914-1921 (Box 75, Folder 883)
  - Autograph book, undated (Box 76, Folder 884)
  - Bank book, 1885-1896 (Box 76, Folder 885)
  - Business journal, 1910-1922 (Box 76, Folder 886)
  - Clippings
    - Politics, 1875-1906 (Box 77)
    - Judicial, 1873-1899 (Box 78)
    - Gubernatorial, 1910-1924 (Box 79)
    - Gubernatorial, 1896; 1912-1921 (Box 80)
    - Gubernatorial, 1913 January-June (Box 81, Folder 887-888)
    - Book reviews, 1898-1921 (Box 82)
    - Miscellanea, 1857-1865 (Box 82)
  - Diaries
    - Extracts, 1851 May 11-1860 May 28 (Box 83, Folder 889)
    - General, 1850s (Box 83, Folder 890)
    - Volume I, 1851 February 5-1857 June 18 (Box 83, Folder 891)
    - Volume II, 1857 June 18-1861 December 13 (Box 83, Folder 892)
    - Volume III, 1861 December 17-1864 June 22 (Box 83, Folder 893)
    - Volume IV, 1864 June 23-1865 June 12 (Box 83, Folder 894)
    - Volume V, 1865 June 13-1870 July 22 (Box 83, Folder 895)
    - Volume VI, 1870 July 30-1877 November 30 (Box 83, Folder 896)
    - Volume VII, 1877 November 30-1892 October 30 (Box 83, Folder 897)
    - Volume VIII, 1892 November 5-1904 December 14 (Box 84, Folder 898)
    - Volume IX, 1914 April 13-1924 August 23 (Box 84, Folder 899)
  - Dissertation: Charles C. Goetsch, "The Journals and Controversies of Simeon E. Baldwin" (photocopy), 1977 April (Box 85, Folder 900-902)
  - Estate records, 1869-1925 (Box 86, Folder 903-904)
  - Financial investment book, 1893-1916 (Box 86, Folder 905)
  - Legal and financial documents, honorary degrees and diplomas, and Yale College diploma, 1861-1915 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Letterbooks, 1871-1877 (Box 87, Folder 906-907)
  - Miscellanea, [ca. l900] (Box 88, Folder 908)
  - Notes, 1876-1904, undated (Box 88, Folder 909-925)
  - Notes, 1899-1917, undated (Box 89, Folder 926-934)
  - Speeches, 1864-1902 (Box 90, Folder 935-944)
  - Speeches, 1903-1911 February (Box 91, Folder 945-952)
  - Speeches, 1911 March-1913 (Box 92, Folder 953-964)
  - Speeches, 1913 April-1915 January (Box 93, Folder 965-973)
  - Speeches, 1915 February-1923 (Box 94, Folder 974-986)
  - Student papers
    - Grades, 1845 (Box 95, Folder 987)
    - Lessons, 1849-1850 (Box 95, Folder 988)
    - Organizations
      - Clio Society, 1850-1860 (Box 95, Folder 989-990)
      - University Quarterly, 1860 (Box 95, Folder 991)
    - Writings
      - Poems and essays, [ca. l849], undated (Box 95, Folder 992)
      - Yale University, undated (Box 95, Folder 993-999)
  - Topical files
    - American Academy of Jurisprudence, 1913 (Box 96, Folder 1000)
    - American Bar Association, 1909-1923 (Box 96, Folder 1001-1005)
    - American Journal of International Law, 1915 (Box 96, Folder 1006)
    - The American State, 1903-1914 (Box 96, Folder 1007)
    - Aviation, 1909-1926 (Box 96, Folder 1008)
    - Church union, 1888-1909 (Box 96, Folder 1009-1011)
    - Clippings, 1863-1885 (Box 96, Folder 1012)
    - Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1914-1918, undated (Box 97, Folder 1013-1021)
    - Connecticut College for Women, 1910-1923 (Box 97, Folder 1022-1023)
    - Gubernatorial campaign, 1910 (Box 97, Folder 1024)
    - Gubernatorial memos, 1911-1913 (Box 97, Folder 1025)
    - Hopkins Grammar School, 1903-1919 (Box 98, Folder 1026-1029)
    - International law, 1900-1922 (Box 98, Folder 1030-1031)
    - Lecture notes
      - Adoption and bastardy, 1917 (Box 98, Folder 1032)
      - American divorce law, undated (Box 98, Folder 1033)
      - American law, 1914 (Box 98, Folder 1034)
      - Andover, 1906 (Box 98, Folder 1035-1036)
      - Bills and notes, undated (Box 99, Folder 1037)
      - Carriers, undated (Box 99, Folder 1038)
      - Case selection, 1907-1917 (Box 99, Folder 1039)
      - Change of domicile, undated (Box 99, Folder 1040)
      - Civil War legislation, undated (Box 99, Folder 1041)
      - Commerce law, undated (Box 99, Folder 1042)
      - Contracts, undated (Box 99, Folder 1043)
      - Corporate bylaws, 1895 (Box 99, Folder 1044)
      - Corporate meetings and elections, 1893 (Box 99, Folder 1045)
      - Corporate officers, 1890 (Box 99, Folder 1046)
      - Corporations, undated (Box 99, Folder 1047-1048)
      - Criminal prosecutions, undated (Box 99, Folder 1049)
      - Death actions, undated (Box 99, Folder 1050)
      - Dissolution of religious corporations, 1893 (Box 100, Folder 1051)
      - Duties to clients, 1902-1914 (Box 100, Folder 1052-1055)
      - Eleemosynary and religious corporations, undated (Box 100, Folder 1056)
      - Extradition, undated (Box 100, Folder 1057)
      - Family disputes, 1901-1917 (Box 100, Folder 1058)
      - Foreign divorce law, undated (Box 100, Folder 1059)
      - Foreign law, undated (Box 100, Folder 1060)
      - Foreign policy, undated (Box 100, Folder 1061)
      - Foreign torts, undated (Box 100, Folder 1062)
      - Insurance partnerships, undated (Box 100, Folder 1063)
      - International family law, undated (Box 100, Folder 1064)
      - Introduction to law school, 1901 (Box 101, Folder 1065)
      - Irish government, 1893 (Box 101, Folder 1066)
      - Land law, undated (Box 101, Folder 1067)
      - Maritime transactions, undated (Box 101, Folder 1068)
      - Marriage, undated (Box 101, Folder 1069)
      - Municipal law, 1889; 1896; undated (Box 101, Folder 1070-1073)
      - Practice, undated (Box 101, Folder 1074-1075)
      - Railroad law, undated (Box 102, Folder 1076-1077)
      - Roman law, undated (Box 102, Folder 1078-1079)
      - Status and classification, undated (Box 102, Folder 1080)
      - Taxation, undated (Box 103, Folder 1081)
      - Transfers of goods, undated (Box 103, Folder 1082)
      - U. S. Constitutional law, 1872-1912; undated (Box 103, Folder 1083-1089)
      - U. S. Constitutional law, 1910; undated (Box 104, Folder 1090-1097)
      - University of Maryland, 1910 (Box 104, Folder 1098)
      - Vassar College, 1917 (Box 105, Folder 1099-1100)
      - Wills, undated (Box 105, Folder 1101-1105)
      - Miscellanea, undated (Box 105, Folder 1106-1108)
      - Miscellanea, undated (Box 106, Folder 1109-1115)
    - Legal cases
      - Church Union cases, 1907 (Box 106, Folder 1116)
      - French spoliation cases, 1801-1851 (Box 106, Folder 1117-1118)
      - Griswold v. Bragg, undated (Box 106, Folder 1119)
      - Hallway Railway Signal Co., undated (Box 106, Folder 1120-1121)
      - Hallway Railway Signal Co., undated (Box 107, Folder 1122-1124)
      - Leffingwell, 1892 (Box 107, Folder 1125-1127)
      - Mary B. Scott, 1886 (Box 107, Folder 1128)
      - Noyes Insurance Co.: scrapbook, undated (Box 107, Folder 1129)
      - Steamer Maryland, undated (Box 107, Folder 1130)
      - Miscellanea, undated (Box 107, Folder 1131)
    - New Haven Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, [ca. l900-1905] (Box 108, Folder 1132)
    - New Haven War Memorial, 1918-1919 (Box 108, Folder 1133-1135)
    - Property
      - Bridgeport, 1910 (Box 108, Folder 1136-1137)
      - Nebraska, 1891-1895 (Box 108, Folder 1138-1139)
      - Railway, undated (Box 108, Folder 1140)
      - Seattle, 1889 (Box 108, Folder 1141-1142)
      - Seattle, 1905-1927 (Box 109, Folder 1143-1147)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore
      - Correspondence, 1910-1911 (Box 109, Folder 1148-1149)
      - Speech, 1910 (Box 109, Folder 1150)
      - Clippings, 1910-1911 (Box 109, Folder 1151)
    - Tax legislation
      - Correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 110, Folder 1152)
      - Papers, 1916; undated (Box 110, Folder 1153-1155)
    - Trumbull Trust Association, 1862-1867 (Box 110, Folder 1156)
    - Yale Law School, 1871-1903 (Box 110, Folder 1157)
    - Yale University, 1914 (Box 110, Folder 1158)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 111, Folder 1159-1164)
  - Writings
    - General, [ca. l890-1900] (Box 112, Folder 1165-1166)
    - The Young Man and the Law, 1916-1920 (Box 112, Folder 1167)
  - Briefs
    - 1865-1874 (Box 113, Folder 1168)
    - 1872-1887 (Box 113, Folder 1169)
    - 1874-1883 (Box 114, Folder 1170)
    - 1878-1886 (Box 115, Folder 1171)
    - 1887-1889 (Box 116, Folder 1172)
    - 1888-1890 (Box 116, Folder 1173)
    - 1890-1891 (Box 117, Folder 1174)
    - 1891-1893 (Box 118, Folder 1175)
    - Miscellanea, 1875-1917; undated (Box 118, Folder 1176)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 119, Folder 1177-1178)
  - Lectures
    - Kent lectures
      - Volume I: Constitutional law, 1870 (Box 120, Folder 1179)
      - Volume II: Constitutional law, 1870 (Box 120, Folder 1180)
      - Volume III: Constitutional law, 1870 (Box 120, Folder 1181)
      - Volume I: Constitutional law, 1874 (Box 120, Folder 1182)
      - Volume II: Constitutional law, 1874 (Box 121, Folder 1183)
      - Volume III. Constitutional law, 1874 (Box 122, Folder 1184)
    - General
      - Civil law, 1872 (Box 122, Folder 1185)
      - Contract law, 1892 (Box 123, Folder 1186)
      - Wills, 1906 (Box 123, Folder 1187)
  - Printed material
    - 1866-1902 (Box 124, Folder 1188-1192)
    - 1903-1918, undated (Box 125, Folder 1193-1196)
  - Oversize material
    - Poster (Simeon E. Baldwin for Governor), house sketch (Brown and Von Beren, architects), and map of Yale field, Circa 1890-1915 (Box 211B)
    - Five indenture deeds and documents, 1617-1898 (Box 211C)
    - Diagram of the Western Railroad Line in Connecticut, sketch of Calvin Coe's land, and sketch for house on State Street and Grand Avenue (New Haven), 1907 and undated (Box 211D)
    - Geological Survey of Connecticut map; maps of properties in Derby, New Haven, and Guilford; maps of U.S. territories and of internal improvements in Virginia, Circa 1848-1889 (Box 211E, Folder 5)
- Roger Sherman Baldwin (1793-1863), 1796-1909; Series VII; 9 linear feet (22 boxes)
  This Series contains material arranged alphabetically by record type.
  - Account books, 1796-1797; 1808-1820 (Box 126, Folder 1197-1199)
  - Account books, 1813-1830 (Box 127, Folder 1200-1201)
  - Account books, 1816-1843 (Box 128, Folder 1202-1204)
  - Account books, 1831-1849 (Box 129, Folder 1205-1207)
  - Account books, 1846-1860 (Box 130, Folder 1208-1210)
  - Bank books, 1819-1861, undated (Box 131, Folder 1211)
  - Biographical sketches, 1863; 1909 (Box 131, Folder 1212)
  - Checks, 1841-1845 (Box 131, Folder 1213)
  - Court dockets, 1834-1847 (Box 131, Folder 1214)
  - Daybooks, 1819-1826 (Box 131, Folder 1215)
  - Daybooks, 1819-1826 (Box 132, Folder 1216)
  - Daybooks, 1847-1862 (Box 133, Folder 1217-1218)
  - Estate papers, 1819-1823 (Box 133, Folder 1219-1220)
  - Journals, 1845-1859 (Box 133, Folder 1221-1223)
  - Legal papers
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1831-1862, undated (Box 134, Folder 1224-1229)
      - Select
        - Butler, J.B., 1847-1848 (Box 134, Folder 1230)
        - Hillhouse family, 1833-1834 (Box 134, Folder 1231)
        - Killingsworth Durham, 1846 (Box 134, Folder 1232)
        - Patent lawsuit, 1858-1861 (Box 134, Folder 1233)
        - Roxbury India Rubber Co., 1839 (Box 134, Folder 1234)
        - Wells vs. Trowbridge, undated (Box 134, Folder 1235)
    - Briefs
      - 1812 (Box 135, Folder 1236)
      - 1817 (Box 135, Folder 1237)
      - 1820-1829 (Box 135, Folder 1238)
      - 1830-1845 (Box 135, Folder 1239)
      - 1831-1832 (Box 135, Folder 1240-1241)
      - 1833-1835 (Box 135, Folder 1242)
      - 1836-1839 (Box 135, Folder 1243)
      - 1838 (Box 135, Folder 1244-1245)
      - 1838-1839 (Box 135, Folder 1246)
      - 1838-1839 (Box 136, Folder 1247)
      - 1839 (Box 136, Folder 1248-1249)
      - 1839 October (Box 136, Folder 1250)
      - 1840 (Box 136, Folder 1251)
      - 1840s (Box 136, Folder 1252)
      - 1840-1842 (Box 136, Folder 1253)
      - 1841 (Box 136, Folder 1254)
      - 1841 (Box 137, Folder 1255)
      - 1842-1847 (Box 137, Folder 1256)
      - 1843-1844 (Box 137, Folder 1257)
      - 1843-1846 (Box 137, Folder 1258-1259)
      - 1845-1846 (Box 137, Folder 1260)
      - 1846 (Box 137, Folder 1261-1262)
      - 1846-1847 (Box 138, Folder 1263)
      - 1847 (Box 138, Folder 1264-1265)
      - 1847-1853 (Box 138, Folder 1266)
      - 1849-1851 (Box 138, Folder 1267)
      - 1855-1857 (Box 138, Folder 1268-1269)
      - undated (Box 139, Folder 1270-1275)
      - undated (Box 140, Folder 1276-1283)
      - undated (Box 141, Folder 1284-1292)
      - undated (Box 142, Folder 1293-1300)
      - undated (Box 143, Folder 1301-1309)
      - undated (Box 144, Folder 1310-1316)
    - Memo books
      - 1832-1853, undated (Box 144, Folder 1317-1318)
  - Papers
    - Gubernatorial, [ca. 1841] (Box 145, Folder 1319-1321)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 145, Folder 1322-1329)
  - Printed material
    - Books: U.S. Constitution, 1851 (Box 145, Folder 1330)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1822; 1838 (Box 145, Folder 1331)
    - Politics, undated (Box 146, Folder 1332)
    - Religion, undated (Box 146, Folder 1333)
    - Speeches, 1844-1850 (Box 146, Folder 1334-1335)
  - Student papers
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 146, Folder 1336)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 147, Folder 1337)
    - Notes, undated (Box 147, Folder 1338)
  - Miscellanea, undated (Box 147, Folder 1339)
- Henry De Forest Baldwin (1862-1947), 1789-1947; Series VIII; 15.5 linear feet (37 boxes)
  - Appointment books
    - 1883-1900 (Box 148, Folder 1340-1345)
    - 1901-1936 (Box 149, Folder 1346-1351)
    - 1919-1936 (Box 150, Folder 1352-1357)
    - 1937-1947 (Box 151, Folder 1358-1361)
  - Letterpress copybooks
    - 1890 Jan 15 - 1897 Feb 2 (Box 152, Folder 1362-1365)
    - 1897 Feb 6 - 1901 Nov 14 (Box 153, Folder 1366-1369)
    - 1903 Nov 6 - 1906 Mar 12 (Box 154, Folder 1370-1371)
    - 1906 Mar 12 - 1907 Nov 25 (Box 155, Folder 1372-1373)
    - 1907 Nov 25 - 1909 Jun 21 (Box 156, Folder 1374-1375)
    - 1909 Jun 22 - 1910 Nov 28 (Box 157, Folder 1376-1377)
    - 1910 Nov 28 - 1912 Feb 16 (Box 158, Folder 1378-1379)
    - 1912 Feb 17 - 1913 Jun 4 (Box 159, Folder 1380-1381)
    - 1913 Jun 4 - 1914 Sep 11 (Box 160, Folder 1382-1383)
    - 1914 Sep 14 - 1916 Jan 26 (Box 161, Folder 1384-1385)
    - 1916 Jan 27 - 1917 Nov 20 (Box 162, Folder 1386-1387)
    - 1917 Nov 21 - 1919 Apr 29 (Box 163, Folder 1388-1390)
    - 1919 Apr 29 - 1920 Oct 13 (Box 164, Folder 1391-1393)
    - 1920 Oct 14 - 1922 Jul 13 (Box 165, Folder 1394-1397)
    - 1922 Jul 13 - 1924 Jan 7 (Box 166, Folder 1398-1400)
    - 1924 Jan 3 - 1926 Nov 12 (Box 167, Folder 1401-1403)
    - 1926 Nov 17 - 1929 Mar 6 (Box 168, Folder 1404-1406)
    - 1929 Mar 6 - 1933 Mar 31 (Box 169, Folder 1407-1410)
    - 1933 Mar 31 - 1937 Dec 16 (Box 170, Folder 1411-1414)
    - 1937 Dec 17 - 1944 Nov 30 (Box 171, Folder 1415-1417)
  - Memo books
    - 1879-1924 (Box 172, Folder 1418-1422)
    - 1925-1946 (Box 173, Folder 1423-1428)
  - Scrapbook, 1875-1897 (Box 174, Folder 1429)
  - Speeches
    - American commerce - Prohibition, 1789-1930 (Box 175, Folder 1430-1440)
    - Roosevelt - Miscellaneous, 1904-1921, undated (Box 176, Folder 1441-1447)
  - Student papers
    - Essays, undated (Box 177, Folder 1448-1449)
    - Lecture notes: Sumner, William Graham, 1883-1885 (Box 177, Folder 1450-1451)
    - Notebooks, 1878-1886 (Box 177, Folder 1452-1453)